Hm?
Dismantle.
That sword...
It specializes in combating cursed spirits,
the Sword of Extermination.
It's packed with the same positive energy
generated by a reverse cursed technique.
If I was a cursed spirit,
that would have eliminated
me on the first blow.
Hmph.
Tastes bad.
You wanna go?
Oh?
You did something, didn't you?
Now that felt odd.
Again?
Cursed energy?
You've done it now!
You can see it, huh?
My technique!
I knew it.
Yamata no Orochi is similar to you.
You follow my slices,
and attack with cursed energy...
Both started happening after
that great wheel revolved.
The incantation of sacred treasures
and that great wheel both represent
perfect cycles and harmony.
Which suggests that this shikigami's ability
is to adapt to anything and everything.
It's the ultimate late-throw
rock-paper-scissors!
In the state I was in back then,
you might have defeated me.
Now you've fascinated me, Fushiguro Megumi!
Domain Expansion:
Malevolent Shrine.
Sukuna's Domain,
It's unlike others in that
it does not cut out a
separate space with a barrier.
Manifesting an innate domain
without sealing it in a barrier
is like using the air as a canvas
to paint a picture.
It's truly a divine feat.
To top it off, by adding a pact to
allow its victims a path of escape,
it vastly increases the range of
its sure-hit effect to
a maximum 200-meter radius.
Though out of consideration for
its effect on Fushiguro Megumi,
Sukuna has currently restrained the effect to
a 140-meter radius limited to the surface.
Anything?
Nope. No signal.
Me too.
Though, I don't think we
need to worry that much.
Huh?
Remember the guy with the
megaphone?
Sukuna's slices are comprised of two types.
The slice that attacks things with cursed energy
in the range of his sure-hit effect is called
"Cleave."
the slice that attacks things
without cursed energy is called
"Dismantle."
Until Malevolent Shrine disappears,
both will rain down endlessly.
The only sure way to
defeat Mahoraga is to bury it,
with the first use of an
attack, before it can adapt.
Cleave would have
fulfilled those conditions,
but that wouldn't necessarily hold true
if it had adapted to slices in general,
rather than to Dismantle.
Mahoraga was close to
finishing its regeneration.
Fuga.